<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>The Everglowin' Blog</title><description>Thoughts, stories and ideas.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><generator>Ghost 0.7</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 19:51:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Preparing Presents for Holly's visit</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Almost a month ago, I have visited Holly in Ireland. She made and got a lot of presents for me... Let me tell you a little about those, so you can understand why I am writing this article.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Colored Balloons&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
This might sound very dorky, but she put a lot&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/preparing-presents-for-hollys-visit/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">78a5ed67-14a6-46ea-8b7b-2e539855c9ca</guid><dc:creator>Lukas A. Müller</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2016 21:05:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Almost a month ago, I have visited Holly in Ireland. She made and got a lot of presents for me... Let me tell you a little about those, so you can understand why I am writing this article.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Colored Balloons&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
This might sound very dorky, but she put a lot of colored balloons into the room I would sleep in. Her focus was on the purple ones, as purple is our both's favorite color. I don't know if I am right, but I think to remember she told me that her sister helped her blowing up the balloons. That was a very fun and warm welcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A thoughtful letter collection&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-276" src="https://everglowin.files.wordpress.com/2016/06/img_20160612_220819597.jpg" alt="IMG_20160612_220819597" width="2510" height="1412"&gt; &lt;br&gt;
As you can see on this photo, she made a letter collection for me. Basically she had written a letter every single day from when we got the tickets for the trip until I would be with her - in Ireland. These were no usual letters, they were and are very thoughtful. She used another color for writing every day and at the end of the day, she would use all of them. All that just so I could 'navigate' and choose a color if I am sad. To be honest... I kind of forgot to use them for when I got sad a little, but I will do that again now! (Especially now that she is in Portugal with her friends for a week as I am writing this).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A very personal green bracelet - From Seville&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-272" src="https://everglowin.files.wordpress.com/2016/06/img_20160612_215245709.jpg" alt="IMG_20160612_215245709" width="4160" height="2340"&gt; &lt;br&gt;
I have once told her that I liked the bracelet of Toby, a class mate of mine with whom I friends. She said, she couldn't find one in purple, especially not with her name on it, because I think to remember I once mentioned i would like one like that, but this one means a lot, she got it on a trip and then it even has this very unique look. I love it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A sweet game: Dragonball Z Sagas &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;[Photo] &lt;br&gt;
Holly got to know over time that Dragonball was a big part of my childhood, and every now and then when I got back home from a place I had to live in (Late December to mid March) with my family, I played a game of Dragonball on my old PlayStation 2 in my room. She told me how she likes to see me playing it, and sometimes, when she had fallen asleep, woke up to the clicking noises of my controller. This present was very cute, even though it is an American version and I can't play it on my console. I will make sure i will be able to play it sooner or later! That's a promise to myself, because she had really researched a lot for me, read reviews and compared prices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Portland Timbers scarf &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;[Photo]&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;This present is more or less not one Holly, but from her mom, but I got to know Holly helped her with it. Of course, how would she know I liked soccer? Holly :3 &lt;br&gt;
Anyways, the colors and also the material of the scarf are so cute, and i liked it so much that i have it hanging over my map now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An Oregon sticker &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;[Photo] &lt;br&gt;
For this one, I am not quite sure if Holly 'contributed' to it, but that doesn't matter. I got it with the scarf, but it is obvious why. Holly and her family live in Portland, which is in Oregon, and by that i do also love this state now. I put it on my Macbook Pro, so i would always think of Holly and the trip every time I'd open it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let's now get to what I want to do for her trip to Germany - to me&lt;/strong&gt;. I can't quite believe she will actually be in the rooms I have been in basically my whole life. Generally the feeling of her getting her is probably what she felt like when I went to her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously, topping her presents is very hard. I probably can't. Everything she has done for me was so cute, and made it the best Birthday ever, especially since it was the most boring one family wise. Well, I turned 16.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But now you probably know why I am writing this article. I want to make an effort and show her my feelings by making and planning things on my own. As a surprise! So let's get to my ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Letter Collection&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
My first idea was of course: Responding to her letter. I think she knows this. I am very bad at keeping presents a secret, and i have accidentally mentioned letters in a message i sent to her on WhatsApp (I always send her status updates when she can't quite look on her phone, so she has a lot of messages when she can check again. She likes to have many)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought about using a different color every week, but that wasn't worth it, as I would just write the letters for around 3 weeks. That would be 3 colors and wouldn't really help in 'navigating'. So I thought about something else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-250" src="https://everglowin.files.wordpress.com/2016/06/img_20160612_213109660.jpg" alt="IMG_20160612_213109660" width="2340" height="4160"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My letter collection wouldn't be loose sheets, bound together like she has done it for me. No, i would get her a notebook or booklet (what we in Germany call notebook). And to make it prettier, more personal and not so boring (As these notebooks usually have bad covers with a number of the lines and stuff on it): a purple cover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[gallery ids="251,252,249" type="rectangular"]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That would not be the only way of differentiating my letters to hers. No. I would add a few creative drawings and other small things to make it very personal and thoughtful. She deserves this more than anything else. She really does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first image (upper left one) is a list of countries we want to travel to. I wanted to make it a little more special than just writing the names down there, so i wrote the country names down in the specific nation's flag and drew their flags beside them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second image (upper right one) was one of a few "I love you's", but this one is written in red (standing for love), surrounded by purple (&lt;span style="color:#800000;"&gt;her&lt;/span&gt;), and then her surrounded by &lt;span style="color:#008000;"&gt;me&lt;/span&gt; (green), because it says &lt;span style="color:#008000;"&gt;I&lt;/span&gt; love &lt;span style="color:#800000;"&gt;you&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The big image shows a conversation we had exactly a week ago as I am writing this, when she went to West Ireland with her family. We both really enjoyed this conversation, as we couldn't facetime or anything else when she had that kind of bad wifi connection. It felt like the old times she said. We used to write a lot like that on WhatsApp. Back then as we weren't calling or facetiming (We weren't a couple back then).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Sweet Welcome Night &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;[Photo of ticket]&lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;I don't know if you can call this a present or surprise, but I want the night she gets here to be special. Well, one problem... She already knows I have gotten tickets for a train ride from Munich to Augsburg. I wanted to get them, because we would have got time to talk in the train on our own (No parents), she could see the landscape of Bavaria and it would remind us of the Dart (train in Ireland). Luckily, she doesn't know exactly all the reasons for why i got the train tickets. That makes it somewhat special still...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Photo of Sushi]
Another part of the surprise is one of her favorite foods: Sushi. I am not quite sure how I will arrange this, but I might just get it ready when I get back from school, so we can eat it at night. I think that would be a sweet thing, because we need something to eat for the next part of this particular surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This part is her favorite movie: Coraline. She had asked me if we could watch it when i was with her, but we kind of forgot about it. This time, I will make sure we won't forget about it and see it right away, to her favorite food. I know she loves moments, as you can read &lt;a href="https://everglowin.wordpress.com/about-holly/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, so I wanted her to have a very special and long one. A whole lasting night 😊.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But before we would do all these things... I will write on a whiteboard that I have. She loves that a lot. I will try to get a purple pen. I haven't found any as i am writing this, but if I won't get one, a usual black one will have to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She will also of course get the letters. And one more present that i will mention now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Self-written Fantasy Story&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;
[Photo of small notebook]
In a small notebook, I have written down a story. A fantasy story of something I am sure of she will like. I have mentioned that in the letter collection, so she would read it again, when she comes across that mention in the letters. But i will make sure she hears me reading it out loud the night she gets here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Her favorite drink: Chai tea&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br&gt;
One surprise I haven't gotten yet is chai tea. She absolutely LOVES chai tea. I will get some, so she has something to drink in the morning. I might also learn how to make tea, I have never tried it out... I know that is weird.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this is about what i came up with as I am writing this. I might extend this article, if there is more i come up with within the next few days. But i wanted to write this before I have to study a lot. I have finals when she get's here 😅.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photos in brackets will follow soon...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>An Everglowin’ Blog</title><description>&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-ydDiBraTgE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello, my name is Lukas, and welcome to this blog! Before I add anything else, I have to mention that I am not the only person writing on here. This page is written by a couple, me &lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;and&lt;/span&gt; Holly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope you will find something that helps or interests you,&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/an-everglowin-blog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">e6c8e46a-ea89-41bb-bfb5-353f63634cda</guid><dc:creator>Lukas A. Müller</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2016 13:31:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-ydDiBraTgE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello, my name is Lukas, and welcome to this blog! Before I add anything else, I have to mention that I am not the only person writing on here. This page is written by a couple, me &lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;and&lt;/span&gt; Holly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope you will find something that helps or interests you, even though at the time this is written, there is not much on here 😀.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you may have noticed, this blog is called "Everglowin'". This is because of a song that was part of us - and we both like -, just a few months before we were a couple: Coldplay's Everglow (as seen above).  If you want to know more about the blog, &lt;a href="https://everglowin.wordpress.com/website/"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more about &lt;a href="https://everglowin.wordpress.com/us/"&gt;us&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://everglowin.wordpress.com/holly/"&gt;Holly&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://everglowin.wordpress.com/lukas/"&gt;me&lt;/a&gt;, just click onto the underlined light-blue colored names.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you once more for visiting! We are hoping to be hearing from you very soon! :)&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>